mathsonline.com.au 2009-10-24

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

We are committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors to our website at http://www.mathsonline.com.au. Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we use and protect information that you provide to us. By using our website and any service we offer via this website you agree to the collection, use and disclosure of your information under the terms of this policy. If you are under 18 please obtain the consent of your parent or guardian before providing us with any information.

**How We Collect Information**

If you subscribe to services on our website you may be asked to provide information such as your name, contact details, and the names of students you intend to use our services.

We may also collect information you submit via any online forms, surveys, message boards, forums or other interactive areas that appear on our websites from time to time.

We may collect information about you if you contact us offline, for example by telephone, fax, email or post.

We may collect information about your usage of our website.

**What We Use Your Information For**

Your information will be used to provide you with access to our website and to supply you with any information, products or services you request.

We may use your information to contact you for feedback on your use or our services or website.

We may also use and analyse the information we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop our websites and the products and services we offer.

**With Whom We May Share Your Information**

We may pass aggregate information about the usage of our websites to third parties but this will not include information that can be used to identify you.

We may share your information with another organisation which buys our company or our assets or to whom we transfer our agreement with you and in the course of any negotiations which may or may not lead to such a transfer or sale.

We will disclose your information if we are required to by law. We may disclose your information to enforcement authorities if they ask us to, or to a third party in the context of actual or threatened legal proceedings, provided we can do so without breaching data protection laws.

Unless permitted or required to do so by law, we will not otherwise share sell or distribute any of the information you provide to us without your consent.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small text files which are transferred from our websites and stored on your computer's hard drive. They enable our website to “remember” who you are.

We use session cookies and persistent cookies to identify and track users who enter the registered areas of our websites. Session cookies are deleted when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will remain on your browser until you delete them. We do not use “spyware”, that is web bugs or hidden identifiers or other similar devices to gain access to information, store hidden information or to trace activities of users.

Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies but if you are using Microsoft’s Internet Explorer or Mozilla Firefox, you should be able to configure your browser to restrict cookies or block all cookies if you wish. If you disable cookies you will still be able to login and use the registered areas of our websites.

**Your Rights**

You have the right to correct any errors in information we hold about you. Please inform us about changes to your details so that we can keep our records accurate and up to date.

You have the right to opt out of receiving any marketing material from us or any third party at any time.

**Security and Retention of Information**

We will keep your information secure by taking appropriate technical and organisational measures against its unauthorised or unlawful processing and against its accidental loss, destruction or damage. We will retain your information for as long as we need it for the purposes set out in this policy, or as otherwise required by law.

**Changes To Our Privacy Policy**

We will from time to time update and make changes to this policy. We recommend that you revisit this privacy policy frequently.

**Links**

If you follow a link from any of our websites to another site, this policy will no longer apply. We are not responsible for the information handling practices of third party sites and we encourage you to read the privacy policies appearing on those sites.
